Visit turkision.com for more!
My son.
Gunduz Bey is alright.
We stitched his wound, he
stopped bleeding thank Allah.
Thank you my Allah.
-Is he conscious?
-He is conscious, my Bey.
He wants to see everyone.
Especially my brother and Elcim Hatun.
Come on then.
Father, stop. Don't push yourself.
Look at her. These wounds are nothing.
-I am alright, no need to worry.
-Gunduz Bey.
Praise be, you look alright. You will be better
if Allah permits.
-Get well soon Gunduz Bey.
-Thank you.
I am healed alright.
We have to see our children's
wedding, right Osman Bey?
You get on your feet first. If Allah permits,
we will ask for her hand in marriage.
It is appropriate. I will get up
until tomorrow, will be at Yenisehir.
Elcim, my daughter. You go too.
Help out with the preparations.
Besides, Ayca is here.
No, father I won't leave
you. I will stay here as well.
You should be there when
Malhun Hatun hears the good news.
This is how it should be. I am alright here.
Besides, you are getting married..
..for our righteous cause,
for the future of our tribes.
From now on, you will first
think about our righteous cause..
..then each other.
From now on, you will have more
enemies than you have friends.
And your wisdom will protect
your hourse first, then your people.
Come on then. We are leaving Gunduz Bey, take care.
You too, Osman Bey.
My daughter, come on.
Alps! March!
You took my castle from me!
You celebrated your victory!
Did you think I wouldn't make you pay for it?
We took what is ours! We will take Atranos as well!
I swear that I will rise..
..on the heads I take from you!
I will die here, however, you will lose.
Shahzade Orhan will get married. Two Kayi Tribes..
..will be one from now on.
I will avenge my valiants..
..who spilled their blood for
the last Shahzade of Seljuks!
Tell me Benjamin. Will Olcaytu give me what I want?
Of course. What will we do with his carcass?
His tribe is next. Bury the alps.
No one must learn about their death for now.
When the time comes, I will send
Uras' head as a wedding gift to Osman.
It will be Osman's death invitation.
O, Kite. We conquered you, however, it was hard.
-Thank Allah, Osman Bey.
-Thank Allah indeed.
-Come on alps.
-My Bey.
There are news from our alp Hasan.
Then, let Imren Tegin know..
..I will be waiting for him..
..at here, Gorklu Valley..
..to give Olcaytu's gifts.
We will be there tomorrow to pick them up.
Do not make promises you can
not hold. Isn't The Atranos Castle..
..is under Osman's siege?
How will Imren Tegin leave from there?
Osman thinks he blocked us by sieging there.
However, there is a way
through passages, do not worry.
What is it, Osman Bey?
While we think we surrounded this dog Imren Tegin..
..he is galloping around us.
What will Olcaytu send to Imren Tegin, my Bey?
We will find out after going to
the meeting area before him.
Konur.
Now, since he got away from this secret passage..
..then, we will continue the siege.
However, you will look everywhere.
-You will find me that passage.
-As you command, my Bey.
My Bey, what about Olivia?
What if Imren Tegin sent them?
Do you hear what you are saying, Alaeddin?
Did Holofira come here to stab me from the back?
-Brother..
-Both Holofira and her aunt..
..guilty or innocent.
It will all be revealed.
Until then, this matter is
done. Son, mind your actions.
We will find out, Osman Bey. If
they know about the passages..
..if they came to the palace
for good or evil, we will find out.
We will find out alright. Orhan.
-My Bey.
-Ready alps.
Now, this message does not only
reveal the agreement between..
..Imren and Olcaytu, but also the
source of information of Mongols..
..how will they ambush us, how
they try to stab us from behind.
Also, the location where they
send messages to Olcaytu.
-Orhan!
-My Bey.
We will destroy this place!
As you command, my Bey.
-Alaeddin!
-My Bey.
Since they came out from that
passage, they might attack the tribes.
-The protection of caravans is on you.
-As you command.
My Bey, what if this Mongol
gives an army to Imren Tegin?
What if we come across an army when we get there?
Tajeddin wanted to stop us before the expedition.
Olcaytu is at the expedition now.
Which means there can't be an army.
If we take his head..
..then the Mongol issue
will be dealth with. Come on!
So Olcaytu Han wants me to take Osman's head..
..in order to give me the
signs I rightfully deserved.
That hound.
I will take what I want in the end, Benjamin.
You will, my Tegin. Olcaytu wants to
make an agreement by giving them to you.
I've waited for this day.
The day that I will get my Seljuks
ancestors' signs has finally come.
My friends.
Today is the day.
Time will witness our victory.
I'm the descendant of Kay Kavus.
The last heir standing.
When I get the signs of my ancestors,
...I will light the dead fire again!
Long live Imren Tegin! Long live
Imren Tegin! Long live Imren Tegin!
This is the blood of Turk.
This is the blood of Byzantine.
Two kins, two powers.
Now I'm asking you. Are you
ready to be my blood fellow...
...for my cause in my path?
We are ready! We are ready!
What do you say about victory?
We swear it shall be ours!
And I swear to you..
I will start my reign with the
blood I shed in these lands!
Now light my victory fire all around!
Destroy all the caravans!
Osman won't be able to trade with anyone anymore!
When he stops collecting gold, he
won't be able to even feed his alps!
Benjamin, destroy everyone on your way.
Show no mercy. Daniel.
Go to Yenisehir and see Olivia.
Elcim Hatun is going to die. That
marriage is never going to happen.
Did you check the rugs and goods well, Gulce?
We shouldn't take flawy goods to Yenisehir market.
All checked one by one, my
Hatun. I separated the flawy ones.
Good. Good. Go inform the
sisters and alps. We're leaving soon.
As you order, Gonca Hatun.
The hostility between you and Osman Bey is over.
He let you go back to your family.
What do you think, Cerkutay?
If my son and wife weren't there...
I want to go there if you let me, my Shahzade.
Are you sure, Cerkutay?
After what happened, neither Osman
nor the alps will stop annoying you.
They will treat you like dirt.
I know about the possible troubles.
But my son and
wife... I have to go.
Alright then. Go back to your family, Cerkutay Bey.
But take my sister to Yenisehir first.
Then you can go meet your family.
Thank you, my Shahzade.
It's good that Cerkutay has
left. I've never trusted him.
Someone betraying Osman
might betray me one day as well.
You're right, my Shahzade.
Look after Gonca, Kanyumaz. Go to Yenisehir
and come back as soon as possible.
As you order, my Shahzade. And what will you do?
I’ll go to Kutahya and discuss
what happened with my father.
Osman is gaining more
power day by day in these lands.
He's going to show me a way.
Who are you? Say your name!
I'm Imren Tegin who Olcaytu sent as the gift.
Commander is awaiting you.
-Only you.
-Get out of my sight!
No trust, no agreement!
If you want Osman's head, you'll do what I say!
-This is it?
Yes, my Shahzade.
Aide Abdul Kasim is in his tent.
We'll advance silently and turn
this demon nest into a grave for them!
-Hasan Alp.
-My Shahzade.
You attack from the side
and take them down silently.
-Oguz Alp.
-My Shahzade?
You take the ones on the other side.
Keep your eyes wide open. I
want no mistakes. Come on.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
We're under attack!
How is that possible? Attack!
Where are you going before
we even talk, Abdul Kasim?
Where were you going?
-Abdul Kasim.
-You can't get anything from me.
You will either speak here...
...or deliver your life.
Stop. Stop.
Now tell me. What are Olcaytu
and Imren Tegin planning?
-Speak.
-Stop. Stop.
They made a deal to destroy Osman.
Olcaytu gave him what he wanted.
-Anything else?
-That's all I know.
Speak!
Olcaytu sent him gold.
-For Osman's head.
-Where is it coming from?
Konya. Through the mountain road.
-Mountain road, Konya?
-Tomorrow.
What else? What else?
-Signs.
-What signs?
-Signs of what?
Sul... Sultan..
You dog! You all will face the same fate.
Gold, huh? We've learned that, my Shahzade.
If Allah permits, my father
will learn the rest. Let's go.
My Ulgen and Ghazi! I'm coming! Wait for me!
Come on, horse! Come on!
Let me meet my son, wife and family!
The way seems so long to you, huh?
Of course it does, Gonca Hatun!
Time isn't ticking! Way isn't ending! But...
Osman Bey has forgiven me.
Even if this way led to China, I would go! Come on!
Osman Bey has a huge heart.
And there is place for everyone. And he's faithful.
He even forgives people
who do things behind his back.
Like he forgave me.
My Bey's heart is as big as this world! But...
...I don't know if there is any
place for me in that huge world.
Well... It won't probably be as it used to be.
You think it won't? He won't trust again?
Would you trust, Gonca Hatun? Well...
He's forgiven me. That's enough for me.
I'll meet my wife and son
and that will make me happy.
May Allah give you a child from
the man you love, Gonca Hatun.
A child holding a sword or a pen.
Come on, horse! Come on!
Let me meet my wife and son!
Come on, faster! To Yenisehir!
Come on! Allah!
Oh... Not now. No, not now!
Oh no. Now what? We have a long way to go.
Ambush! Alps, ambush!
-Are you alright?
-Yes, you?
I'm good.
Kanyumaz, go after those dogs!
-Find out who is holding their leashes!
-As you order, Gonca Hatun.
-Are you alright?
-Yes. You?
I'm alright. Fine.
-Alps.
-Yes, Alaaddin Bey?
Go inform Mehmed Bey about
the attacks on the caravans.
-As you order, my Shahzade.
-Alps, stop.
-My brother isn't here. He's gone to Kutahya.
-Then you're alone, huh?
Stay among the women in
Yenisehir until Mehmed Bey is back.
Don't go back. This spot is closer to Yenisehir.
No need. We can take care
of ourselves, Alaaddin Bey.
You mind your own matter.
How sullen she is!
Allah is eternal!
Come on.
Give me my trust back, Alaeddin Bey.
It's not your trust. This
dagger is mine, did you forget?
How long has the dagger you returned been yours?
I won't give it to you. I won't
give this dagger to anyone.
This is the gift of the woman I love.
You gave up on that love,
Alaeddin. Give me my dagger.
I won't give it to you, Gonca. -Give it to me.
-I won't...
Give it to me!
We must go now. My son is waiting.
Cerkutay Bey. Your arm is alright, right?
Ghazi Alp will get happy when he sees you.
It's alright, my Shahzade, thanks to you.
He will get happy, but...
...children call Ghazi "son of a spy".
I don't know how we are going to silence them.
They don't know, Cerkutay Bey. They don't know.
No one knows what others feel.
The cart is ready. We can set out, my Shahzade.
Good. Let's go then. Coy Hatun, come.
I guess you were going to call me Spy Hatun.
No... I was going to call you Thief Hatun.
A thief who steals hearts.
Visit turkision.com for more!
Olcaytu Khan cannot kill the executioner, right?
Let's drink then.
If you fail after all these demands...
...Olcaytu will kill you, Imren Tegin.
Don't worry... I will bring Osman's head to you.
Now..
Bring me my gifts. I need them...
...for Osman's head.
What's the rush for?
We will give you all the power you need.
-Then what?
How am I going to trust Olcaytu?
-Are you saying that?
Weren't you the one who allied
Vatican, the Papal knights...
...criminals, and fugitives...
...the Crusaders with the Ilkhanids?
That's right. I'm not the one who should be scared.
Osman is. -Now listen carefully.
When the Crusader army crosses
Osman's lands and reaches Konya...
...you'll be Olcaytu's favorite.
With this power, you'll strike
Osman. You'll take his lands.
As the grandson of Kay Kavus, the heir...
...you'll establish your state...
...with the trusts of the Seljuk dynasty.
And with those trusts..
...I'll receive the support of...
...Osman's tribes, won't I?
Olcaytu allows you because of that.
With one condition..
...a state loyal to the Ilkhanids.
Is anything else possible in this world, Imren?
I will use my power within Byzantium...
...to conquer their lands.
When Olcaytu finishes the Eastern
war, he'll turn his route to the West.
That's when your lands will be our headquarters.
Bring the trusts, let's see...
...the Seljuk trusts.
Not yet, not yet.
Welcome.
How is Gunduz Bey? Alps said he was injured.
Gunduz Bey is alright, but...
..I have different news for you.
What is it?
Good news first.
-Don't keep me guessing, tell me!
What do you want the most, Malhun?
A daughter-in-law, right?
But Turkmen daughter-in-law, Bala mother.
And she...
...also wants her to be Muslim.
Will my Orhan..
Prepare the dowery, Malhun Hatun.
Orhan accepted marrying Elcim.
I knew it... I knew Orhan would make
the best decision, thanks to my Allah.
May it be blessed, my daughter. I am glad.
-Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
Tomorrow morning when Gunduz Bey arrives
they said we'll do as our customs order us...
...and ask for the girl's hand in marriage.
Then let's quickly start preparations.
We have a lot to do, come on.
My Fatma. What are you worried about?
I am worried about my brother, Ulgen sister.
Doesn't Shahzade Orhan love Holofira?
What will happen to Holofira now?
Allah Allah... Why do you care about Holofira?
He's interfering in the issues
of adults with the height of a leg.
Good! I hope they find another
Hatun for that long Shahzade...
...so I can marry Gonca.
Sure, sure, you can marry Gonca, Ghazi.
How do you manage to talk
about Gonca every time, Ghazi?
I am telling you! Because I love her!
Give me patience, my Allah!
You will signify your loyalty...
...and stamp your seal.
Never without seeing the trusts.
You never compromise.
Bring them!
Sultan Alaeddin Keykubat's ring.
I see.
So you had these all this time, huh?
The proof of your allegiance.
Don't make a mistake, Imren. Don't.
Stamp your seal, so the
lands you step on will be yours.
There is an issue, Commander.
These lands are already mine.
In my lands, we seal the agreements with blood.
Take them! Take them!
We will wait for our prey, for Imren.
I don't want to cast a shadow
on your happiness Malhun, but...
...we have an issue.
I know Bala, I know.
Holofira and Olivia, right?
Osman Bey thinks there are passages which
Imren uses to get in and leave Atranos.
What are you saying?
Then Olivia knows..
-Now our duty...
...is to make Olivia speak and
learn more about those passages.
Andra... What happened? Did something happen?
-My Hanim..
Orhan Bey...
...will marry Elcim Hatun.
Don't worry, this is the last tear I shed.
Orhan is a Shahzade. He has
to think about his Beylic's future.
Holofira what are you saying? Orhan loves you!
And you love him! How can you accept this?
Orhan is doing the right
thing. He is walking on a way.
Our love can't be more important
than the future of his people.
What about us? What about our people?
You have to marry Orhan to take our castle
back! Or else, we will lose everything!
Will you still give up on Orhan?
-Tell me your name.
-Imren Tegin.
Here.
Welcome, Executioner.
Konur.
He is my executioner.
You figured things out again,
Osman. You came here before me.
However, I will take what is mine.
With Allah's permission,
we will take your life today.
You still think of me like one of your enemies.
I am the only person that can kill you.
May everyone be my witness..
..that you can not take my life. Alps!
My treasures..
-Two executioners are a lot for these lands.
-Right, one of us has to go.
You will be buried to these
lands that you poisoned before!
I will take it if I said so, Osman.
Where are you?
First, one of you. Then, all of you.
I will bury all of you into these lands!
Olivia. The information you
gave was true, thank you.
I hope I earned your trust.
As we are still locked in our rooms, Bala Hatun.
No. Trust is not earned so easily, Olivia.
If you are true with your intentions..
..you will tell us about the
secret passages of Atranos.
-Secret passages?
-Why are you surprised?
Don't you know about the secret
passages under your castle?
Or were you playing tricks from the start?
Olivia? Why did you come to this palace?
We told you many times, Malhun Hatun.
There is no trickery. We
are after saving our lives.
If there is no trickery, then
where are the secret passages?
My people, my tribe is in danger. If
your intentions are true, then tell us.
There is no secret passage that we know of.
Old passages crumbled down years ago.
You are lying right into our faces.
However, we know you well.
You must've dug out a tunnel..
..to run away while your castle is under siege.
Enough. How many times do we have to tell?
If you do not believe us,
take our lives or let us go.
Your lives are entrusted to us, Holofira.
Our intention is to learn the truth.
Bala Hatun, yes..
..we used to have secret
passages just like every other castle.
However, these passages crumbled down years ago.
After that, all exits were sealed.
How did Imren got out if there are no
secret passages, then it must be open again.
It is impossible. Even if Imren
Tegin finds out about their location..
..there is no way for him to open
them up again in such a short time.
However, it does not matter what we say.
From what I can see, you will not believe us.
If you were in my stead,
would you believe it Holofira?
Bayindir Bey and our alps died
while you were in that castle.
How can I believe you now?
There is no need to say more.
Come on, aunt.
Osman. You play many tricks..
..and think that you would fool me. You idiot.
I was waiting for this moment for years.
I always dreamt about this moment.
Finally, my dreams are in my hands.
-What is it?
-How can this be?
Osman!
Even I couldn't hold him, the
precaution you took saved me, my Bey.
I could not hold him either. My Bey..
-..this dog turned out to be tough.
I haven't seen someone fight like this.
He escaped from us with a single move.
My Bey, this Seljuks Sultan
signs, will add to our power, right?
Of course it will, brother.
We've gained a great victory.
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah who granted us this day.
These are the last remains
of Turk's glorious state.
They were using these as a trump card for so long.
This is the sword of Grand Keykubad.
This was not forged to be
left in hands of the enemy.
Now, put them away for now.
This Imren Tegin said this fight
would not be over before one of us dies.
Then, we want his head, not these treasures.
As long as he lives, Rome would revive..
..and there would be disorder
among Turks. That is why..
-..we will kill that dog.
What will do with these, my Bey?
The sky can only have one sun.
I know what we will do. Come on then.
Alaeddin Bey.
I don't want to stay at the palace. Let me go.
Are you afraid of my mother and father?
They have forgiven you.
Why don't you forgive me..
..and we will stay here?
-Alaeddin Bey.
What you say is not so easy. Do not dream about it.
So you will make it hard, Coy Hatun.
Alright then. Make it hard, it is your right.
Say whatever you want, do whatever
you want, I won't say anything.
However, forgive me.
My son.
-Gonca.
-Mother?
-Are you alright?
-We are alright, mother.
Just as we thought, Imren's
men attacked the caravan.
-Are you alright, my daughter?
-I am alright, Bala Hatun.
Mehmed Bey went to Kutahya.
I did not want them to return
to the Frontier Marketplace.
However, Gonca Hatun still
does not want to stay, mother.
Gonca. You heard Osman Bey, right?
The past is in the past.
Do not feel bad. This is your home also, come on.
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
Kismet, prepare a room for Gonca.
And keep your eyes open.
Don't you trust Gonca Hatun, my Hatun?
She's a good girl, did things for her family.
But she made a mistake once, Kismet.
And this is about my son.
You got this.
Mother, I'm telling you I heard Gonca Hatun.
-Just let me go.
-Hey. Look at me.
Don't go crazy when you see
her. Stop bothering her, Ghazi.
Shh... Get behind me.
-Mother, let me go first.
-Hey, come here. Get back.
Stay here.
Ghazi, your father is here...
Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
-Cerkutay!
Did you kill my father?
-Cerkutay, wake up.
-Father!
-Cerkutay.
-Father.
-Cerkutay? What are you doing?
-Who are you?
-What is this place?
-What?
What do you mean? I'm Ulgen,
your hatun. This is your son Ghazi.
-Osman Bey...
-Mother.
My father thinks I'm Osman Bey.
Luckily, he remembers Osman Bey but...
-He doesn't remember us.
-I just hit him and he lost his mind.
Father, this is us! Don't you remember?
Your father would never forget you!
My boy! Your father is back!
-Just for you, Ghazi!
-My father! He remembers me!
I would never forget you,
boy. We are back together!
We will never be separated again!
I have a little question. You remember me?
Cerkutay...
Look at me. If you say you don't hear me...
..or don't remember me
...I will just break your head!
I would never forget you, my Hatun.
-You serious?
-Yes.
Look around well. You'll bring
things here from now on. Alright?
I'm glad you're here.
You and I will get along well.
But we need to find a name for you.
If you can't hear or speak,
...your name shall be Mute.
They are beautiful! The
fabric I've been looking for!
Were there any spies among the
warriors? You're supposed to spy.
We thought Osman's alps killed
you. What are you doing here?
I came here as a prisoner
and entered Osman's palace.
They think I can't speak or
hear. They feel pity for me.
Good. Good. Their mercy will bring their end.
Here.
I was going to give this to Olivia.
But you can deliver it more easily.
Listen well. With Imren Tegin's orders.
You need to poison Elcim.
Where has she gone? She doesn't know around! Mute!
Mute!
Mute! Stay with me. Or you may get lost.
Let's go to the palace!
I didn't believe any of your words.
I have no intention to make you believe.
Imren killed all the lords...
Why did he leave
your aunt alive?
My aunt didn't
accept his wishes.
Now we are here because he wants to kill her.
-I care about my tribe and people.
If you know about the passages... -Look.
You don't know me.
If I knew where those passages were...
...I would kill Imren and take my castle back...
...not come here and take shelter.
Good. For now, I believe you.
I hope you can take your
castle back as soon as possible.
Thank you.
Look, Elcim. You see me as
your opponent, but you should not...
I just want to get rid of Imren..
...and go back to my castle.
Now, if you allow me...
Yunus Emre...
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Peace be upon you too. Thanks to Him,
Who united our ways. It's been a long time, huh?
You're returning from one war and heading
into another, aren't you, Orhan Bey?
I am going to the biggest one, Yunus Emre.
I made an important decision
for the state. But my heart...
...my heart is in flames. And I am
going to the palace now to face that fire.
You chose hegira, huh?
The Messenger of Allah...
..loved the Kaaba so much.
He resisted staying in Mecca
despite all the oppression and hardship.
You know... But when it became...
...impossible to teach the
Islamic cause in Mecca...
...he migrated to Medina. He preferred to...
...miss the Kaaba for the cause of Islam.
And the cause of Islam grew in Medina.
One of the most significant
events that contributed
to the conversion of
the polytheists to Islam...
...and the purification of Mecca from idols...
...was the migration...
...of The Messenger of Allah to Madinah.
Now, it is your turn to migrate.
I know your heart is burning.
But that fire will lead to great
reward in the future, who knows?
Because you prioritize the cause of Islam
over your heart's cause.
Since it is our duty...
...it is our obligation to do what is
necessary for the future of both Beylics.
Even if a thousand hearts of mine turn to ashes...
...for the sake of the world
of Islam, I will not be upset.
I won't be sad, but...
What about her?
Everyone's deed book is
different. Everyone's test is different.
The test is a means, an opportunity...
...to guide a person to the right path.
Each of us will see that test as a means...
...to become an honest and
fair person. May Allah let us...
...be victorious over the tests
that are heavy on our nafs.
Aameen.
O Allah...
In the name of Allah!
Brother... The water has boiled. Give it to me.
Allah..
Brother... What is this?
Alps will eat this, not horses!
That's the best I can do with a dagger, brother.
If Cerkutay Bey was here, he would chop them well.
Nevermind, Alps. We can still eat them, right?
Konur Bey... My Bey will also
eat this, that's why I am asking.
-Aykurt!
-My Bey.
Did your Bey grow up in a palace, huh?
We are used to such tables. Come on now... Come on.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
My Bey... We have onions as well, you like them.
Thank you, thank you
-Here, my Bey.
-Thank you. Praise be.
Praise be.
My Bey. There is no trace of Imren Tegin.
Don't worry. He will find us when his death comes.
-Come on, go and eat.
-Yes my Bey.
Oh praise be, what is this?
-Aykurt!
-My Bey..
Maybe you should become
a cook, not the Head of Alps.
Don't,my Bey. Do not separate me and my sword.
Don't my Bey, your Head of
Alps is talented, but I need him.
If that's what you are saying...
...then from now on, you will cook the meals!
Please, don't my Bey. Still, we will do as you say.
-Bring me the trusts.
-Yes my Bey.
Elcim... Can I come in, my daughter?
Sure, Malhun Hatun.
We will ask for your hand tomorrow, I
wanted to check if something's missing.
Thank you, Malhun Hatun. You hold
me in high regard. I have everything.
We are doing our duty, my daughter.
Tomorrow, with Allah's
consent, we will give this a name.
I have known you well, and I
believe you will be worthy of my Orhan.
But the way you will walk on
will not be a garden of roses.
You will struggle with many
tests, you know that right?
I do.
But this is more of a test for
Orhan Bey than it is for me.
You are a smart girl, Elcim. I know
Holofira's presence here disturbs you.
But this is the issue of the state.
Sending back someone seeking
refuge wouldn't suit us, my daughter.
Even if you call it the state's
issue, Orhan Bey loves Holofira.
I know, I can see it. But I don't trust Holofira.
I hope Orhan Bey will not show a weakness
which will prevent two Beylics from uniting.
I gave up on myself. I just
care about Kayi's future.
O, the Seljuk...
My ancestor Alparslan opened
the path of gaza for us in Malazgirt...
...with his blood and his sword...
My grandfather Suleyman
Shah walked all the way to Iznik...
He sent Crusaders back. He
even made Konya the capital city.
He destroyed many crusaders and
turned many lands into our homeland.
And Alaeddin Keykubat...
The most powerful period of the Seljuk...
...was during the reign of Alaeddin Keykubat.
This empire, once considered invincible...
...is now about to collapse.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Tell me, why? Why?
Because they made many
mistakes. They fought for the throne.
And they did not rule with justice.
Thus... There were rebellions.
If Allah permits...
-If Allah permits we won't make the same mistakes.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
We will never let them question our control.
And we will first rule with justice.
We will not make that mistake. We won't...
...and our state will be everlasting.
My Bey... Why are we burying these trusts
when we could gain strength with them?
Our way and our cause are the same.
But we won't rule with a trust..
...we will rule with justice.
And our swords will secure the justice.
The one who stands in the
shadow does not cast a shadow.
With Allah's consent, I hope,
we will spread our shadow everywhere.
-If Allah permits my Bey.
If someone takes these trusts one day and...
...says, "I am also one of the heirs"...
...it will surely be difficult.
Thus..
...it is time to bury them in history.
We will commemorate The State of Seljuks..
..with its glories and legacies.
Alright then.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Alps, seal the cave exit.
This, if Allah permits, is the end of an era,
and the beginning of a new one.
May Allah open our paths.
-Ameen.
-Ameen, my Bey.
So, from what I've heard,
Shahzade Orhan is getting married.
Now it is that tall Shahzade's turn.
You do not forgive the tall Shahzade, right?
For real, Gonca will you not forgive my brother?
Fatma Hatun, do not confuse Gonca Hatun.
Shut it Gazi.
Look here Gazi, I actually love you more.
-Really?
-Really.
However, you are just a kid. What can we do?
Are we allowed, Gonca Hatun?
No you are not, Shahzade!
Gazi, come on Gazi.
-We shall leave you to talk.
-I will come back Gonca Hatun!
Don't you forgive tall Shahzade!
Come on, move!
So I have a fierce opponent, Trickster Hatun.
-Gonca.
-Yes? What is it Alaeddin Bey?
Gazelle-eyed Hatun.
-Shall we speak now? -Of course.
No medicine would close the wound I made, I know.
They did not teach me how to tend to the wound..
..a lover makes at the school.
I made a mistake. However, I did not know.
-What did you learn? -I learned everything.
-Ulgen Hatun told me everything.
-Ulgen..
Why you told me you don't love me.
That you didn't do your duty, to not betray me..
..that you given up on me.
The blows you took..
..I was not with you.
You were correct. I left you alone.
However, it is over now. Past is in the past.
I swear to you, I will make you forget all the
trouble you had to endure because of me.
What if you don't believe me again?
How can I trust you, Alaeddin?
Besides everything, what about your family?
How will they trust a Hatun
that is known for being a spy?
Gonca. I promise to you..
No matter what happens, no matter what they say..
..I will always be your side.
Did you forgive me?
What difference would it make?
Don't you know of my brother? And my mother?
Alaeddin, don't you know of my mother? No..
-..no Alaeddin it cannot happen.
-Don't say no.
If you forgive me..
..we have enough strength
to overcome every obstacle.
That is what I fear the most.
I am afraid of your bravery, Alaeddin.
Look, I can't predict what my brother can do.
This is a great issue.
This would make Kayis and Germiyanids enemies.
There will not be such a war.
I am saying to you, I am ready
to face every obstacle with you.
Tell me now. Forgive me.
Alright, I forgive you.
-Allah!
-Stop, I am still mad at you.
Finally, thank Allah.
You forgive me.
-My Gonca.
-Yes?
-Now, free my name.
-No.
There is still time for that.
-My Gonca.
-I forgive you.
-Leave now.
-I was thinking about a horse race..
..would be good for you anger.
Come on Alaeddin.
-Come on, Alaeddin.
-My Gonca.
-Come on now, Alaeddin Bey.
Ulgen? Why would Malhun
Hatun call me to the kitchen?
Is it because..
-It is..
-..not Malhun Hatun who called you.
-It was not my mother who called you.
It was me, Lord's daughter.
-Orhan Bey.
-Holofira.
Listen to me.
What will we talk about?
You learned everything.
-I wanted you to hear from me first.
-It would've changed nothing.
-You are doing what is right.
-Holofira, look.
I've thought about it a lot.
However, I could not find a way.
-For my State, for my family, I had to.
-I know your truth.
No other thing would fit you anyway.
However, I will never leave by your side, Holofira.
I will never give up on you.
What will you do? Will I be your
second wife like your mother?
Alright. Let us say I accept,
you crushed my honor..
..what about Elcim? Will she accept it?
What about your mother? They do not trust me.
They are looking for excuses to blame me.
When we get married, will
they really take me to their side?
Will they really trust me? No.
I will still be the first one to blame.
-Holofira, look..
-Elcim Hatun..
..is both Turk and a muslim.
She is also from your blood.
She is the right wife for you.
There is no need to force anything.
Holofira, do not do this. If you love me..
..even a little bit, think about it a little more.
I loved you a lot, Orhan Bey.
However, it over now.
Now, you will do everything for your State
and I will do everything for my castle.
That is all.
You are the woman I love,
and will always love, Holofira.
Never forget this.
I need to go now.
Come in.
I didn't want anything.
But Imren Tegin wants something very important.
Who are you?
This is yours. We're on the same side.
Imren Tegin wants us to poison Elcim.
Your being here will make
things much easier for me.
Pour this poison into Elcim's drink.
But the blame will be put on Holofira.
You don't even avoid risking your niece.
This is the only way. Orhan will
rebel against his father for Holofira.
And two Kayi Beys will fight each other.
We'll destroy them by dividing.
And Holofira will never suspect me.
Because she thinks I want to collaborate
with Osman and take my castle back.
I have many things to learn from you.
Poison Elcim as soon as possible then.
Because the real game will start afterwards.
They'll kill Holofira when she's blamed.
You know that, right?
Orhan will never let that happen.
What if he fails?
Holofira will be honored with
a blessed death for our lands.
Visit turkision.com for more!
Listen carefully now.
When Crusaders go beyond Osman's lands
and reach Konya...
...you'll be Olcaytu's favorite man.
With that power, you will
hit Osman and take his lands.
As the descendant of Kay
Kavus, Governor of Seljuks,
...with the signs of Seljuk dynasty we'll give you,
...you will establish your state.
You made your game, Imren Tegin.
But I swear I will..
...bury you and Crusader looters...
...in these lands.
And I will break Olcaytu's alliance with Crusaders.
I swear I will never let...
...dogs like you in these lands.
Ever.
You never listen, Kanyumaz.
I still have your family.
But you're keeping your nose up.
I will save my family from you, you vile man!
Get him up.
I would cut off your head but I need you.
Uraz Bey's head.
Take this to Osman as my wedding gift.
Osman Bey is going to make you pay for this!
I will be waiting for him in Uraz's tribe.
Tell him to bring me what is mine.
Take him.
Osman Bey is coming!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Peace be upon you too.
-Welcome, my Bey.
-Thank you. Thank you.
Osman Bey. You're back victorious, I hope.
Well, has anyone ever seen me
coming back with empty hands?
You've stood up so fast,
Gunduz Bey? Are you alright?
I'm fine. Heart affairs must
be handled fast, they say.
Well... Did your tribe settle?
-My people are settling.
And I spread five small tribes around it.
Shepherds must be looking for meadows already.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Let's get this handled.
Come on then. Let's get
to the girl-asking ceremony.
Let's go.
Holofira, you are making a mistake.
Orhan is going to get engaged with her shortly.
-You can stop that if you want.
-Aunt, please.
I said my final words. Orhan will do his part.
-So will I.
-You will regret this badly, Holofira.
Don't you want your castle?
When Orhan and Elcim get engaged
...two beylics will get united and take
our castle back. You'll get what you want.
Beg to Jesus Christ for no obstacles.
I've seen this blessed day.
Two Kayi tribes have become one state.
-I would nothing else in this world.
-Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Don't worry.
We'll have better days together,
If Allah permits.
By accepting this, our children...
...will both start a family...
...and give the biggest
support to our blessed dream.
Thank you, children.
Ulgen, bring the sherbet.
Let's start sweet and finish so.
Everybody knows why we have gathered here.
Starting a family and providing peace for it...
...is as hard as being a state.
Actually, it's even harder.
I'd do everything keep my son Orhan safe.
And he is as fearless as a lion.
To be worthy of the dream of being a state,
...he grew up with the state manners.
-Praise be.
-Well... With daughter Elcim
...he will shoulder this cause.
Allah sent us to these frontiers
to establish a statei and If Allah permits.
...He will let us be a state
to rule all over the world.
-If Allah permits, If Allah permits.
-And this marriage...
...will be one of the biggest steps.
Well... no need for more words.
With the command of Allah
and the word of Prophet (PBUH),
..I want Efendize Elcim Hatun...
...for my son Shahzade Orhan.
I'm Gunduz Bey, Bey of Kayi.
We've gone through a lot of troubles.
A storm flew us to the frontiers.
Thankfully, Osman Bey helped us.
-Thank you, thank you.
-All the trouble...
...made my daughter Elcim stronger than before.
Your dream is my dream, Osman Bey. I follow you.
And my daughter, who is my
only wealth will follow Orhan Bey.
If your dream is the state, we'll
establish it at the cost of our lives.
For sure. For sure.
Let's get to the point.
I can't find a
better son-in-law...
...than Osman Bey's son Orhan Bey.
The girl is yours.
Thank you. Thank you. Come on then.
Let's have a great wedding, huh?
-Come on.
-In the name of Allah.
May it be blessed, my daughter. May it be blessed.
-My son...
-May it be blessed.
-Thank you my Bey.
May it be blessed. May it be blessed.
-My beautiful daughter.
May you have a family and
a lineage together If Allah permits.
-My son.
-May it be blessed, my daughter.
-May Allah allow you to complete it, I hope.
-Thank you mother.
My sister...
Brother.. -Brother..
We were both destined to love
but not be together, huh Holofira?
We might not be together, Gonca.
This is what love is.
We loved each other so much. We loved each other
so much that we gave up on our love.
Come on.
The tribe fell, Imren
Tegin. We killed all the Alps!
Come, Osman. I have things to talk to you.
What are we going to do to
women and children, Imren Tegin?
Keep the prisoners. I will use them against Osman.
Gonca Hatun..
What happened Kanyumaz? What happened to you?
-Imren...
I brought news from Imren Tegin.
Kanyumaz, stop! What happened? Tell us!
I fell into the trap of Imren Tegin.
Our Alps died. They let me survive.
What does that dog want? Huh?
What does he want, Kanyumaz?
He wanted me to take Uraz Bey's head to Osman Bey.
Oh no... No... Come on!
Come on, we have to go to the palace now!
Uraz Bey...
The fate of these lands
once again depends on a war.
It is evident that Olcaytu Khan and
the Pope made an agreement...
The formation of the Crusader army proves it.
Imren Tegin is stronger than we thought.
These lands will witness a
greater war than ever before, right?
Either we win this war...
...or we'll break the Ilkhanate-Crusader
alliance. There's no other way.
Thank you, Osman Bey. Know that we'll stand by you
until the last drop of our blood.
But Imren will do everything...
...to take those trusts from you.
-Yes, that's right.
He'll attack even more fiercely than before. But...
...we will never let them
fight on these fertile lands.
-With Allah's consent, we will destroy them.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
Orhan. -My Bey.
The gold that Olcaytu Khan will
give to Imren.. You will go and take it.
Yes my Bey. Before Olcaytu Khan's
dirty gold sinks our lands into the mud..
..I will go and take it with Allah's consent.
-Thank you my son, thank you.
Praise be to my son, praise be!
-Father!
-Alaeddin!
-Father..
-My son...
-What happened?
-Father...
-We have important news, my Bey.
-Tell him, Kanyumaz.
Osman Bey... Imren Tegin stopped
me on the way and killed my Alps.
-He martyred Uraz Bey, my Bey.
-What are you saying?
What are you saying?
Indeed, to Allah we belong
and to Allah we shall return.
He wanted me to tell you that he is
waiting for you in Uraz Bey's tribe alone.
First, Bayindir Bey...
...now Uraz Bey, huh? It
is time to kill that dog now!
Osman Bey, stop. I will not leave
you alone. I will come with you.
Besides, that dog might play a game.
Alright, alright. Orhan!
My Bey.
Send news to our Alps.
Tell them to go to all the tribes.
That dog might attack our
tribes. They must take precautions.
Yes my Bey. -Go, my son.
-Alaeddin!
-My Bey...
You will protect this place, my son.
Don't worry about it, my Bey. May you come back
with good news If Allah permits.
Good. Konur!
Prepare all of our Alps!
-We need to take that dog's head!
-Yes my Bey. -Come on.
My Bey...
What happened, Kanyumaz?
-My Bey...
Imren Tegin.. beheaded Uraz Bey.
He also... attacked our caravan.
And now... he is waiting for
Osman Bey in Uraz Bey's tribe.
My father was right. He
told me not to trust Osman..
...and this dog who approached for trades.
I will go there with Osman Bey
and question him about this raid.
Orhan Bey...
I want to discuss the issue that disturbs me.
Tell me Elcim Hatun. I am listening to you.
Holofira... While she's here, neither will
there be a wedding, nor will the tribes unite.
Here we are...
May it be good, Elcim Hatun. Did something happen?
What else do you expect? She's
the daughter of enemy lands.
She will only cause issues in these lands.
If she stays here, there
will be bloodshed. Know that.
Elcim Hatun. You are from Hayme mother's lineage..
...you are brave, you are a Bey's daughter...
I can always vouch for you.
But Holofira... I've known her since childhood.
I can also vouch for her.
Holofira is a good and honourable
person who never has bad intentions.
Good... So that you know her well..
...if she makes a mistake,
you will be responsible for that.
Thanks to Allah, we have prepared everything.
Malhun? Why are you sad instead of being happy?
I am worried, Bala. Olivia
and Holofira are still here.
I cannot trust them. I am afraid
Orhan might make a mistake.
You are right. You are right. The test
of Orhan and Holofira is really difficult.
We need to solve this as soon as possible.
Even if Holofira is innocent, she needs
to leave the palace as soon as possible.
Or else... I don't even want to
think about what is going to happen.
Anyway... Forget about me. I couldn't ask you
because I was dealing with my own problems.
What do you think about Gonca?
What is going to happen to them?
I don't know Malhun. Believe me, I don't know.
Gonca saved Alaeddin's life.
She loves him enough to
give up on her life, it's obvious.
But... I am worried about Mehmed, Bala.
Mehmed... He acts without thinking.
What if he does something to
Alaeddin? It won't just affect my son...
...it will turn two Beylics into
enemies. There might be a war, Malhun.
If they shed blood, there will be a disaster.
But... it's not just that.
Let's assume we convinced and stopped Mehmed.
Gonca... Do you trust Gonca, Bala?
She will attend our meetings if they get married.
-We will share the secrets of our state.
-That's what I ask myself every day.
Do I trust Gonca?
My heart says... "This is love.
Her love for Alaeddin will outweigh everything.
She won't betray us again."
But... what if something
happens between us and
Germiyans? With her
family on the other end...
...will she still be on Alaeddin's side, our side?
We will see what she is going to
when her family is involved, Bala.
May my Allah protect our children.
Ameen, Bala Hatun.
How are they still keeping
this girl at the castle, aunt?
You will see, there is something behind this.
Enough of this. Stop thinking about it.
-Look, if this girl bothers you this much..
-It is not about me, aunt.
I am thinking of my tribe.
What if Imren attacks our tribe?
I know, you are trying to
protect your tribe, Elcim.
Now, if your brother, my valiant soldier lived..
..he would've carried all this weight.
Then, I would be the Hatun of a Bey.
-We would divide all this trouble with my valiant.
-Aunt.
Now, all this weight is on your shoulders.
I know your pain.
You are entrusted to us from my
brother. Do not think yourself a burden.
No. I do not think like that.
However, I feel sorry for you, Elcim.
You are marrying with Orhan, a Shahzade.
This weight would be heavier.
And you will carry this alone.
Still, my aunt. This is my destiny.
Alps are ready, my Bey. They
are waiting for the ambush.
Their commander is coming, my Bey.
Let him come.
There will not be war. Women
and the people are our captives.
If you draw a sword, will
kill both women and children.
Look here!
You haven't seen the sharp side of our swords!
So keep it short. Open this road.
Imren Tegin wants to see you
alone at the tribe, Osman Bey.
Our decision is this. You will
see each other alone, otherwise..
Shut it!
Who are you? I am not here to talk with a servant!
Open this road! Or I know how to make you.
-Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
-Solgur Aga.
-Yes, my Bey.
You will find me those captives.
Even if they vanish.
You will find them and bring them to me.
-As you command, my Bey.
Osman Bey, be careful. There
dogs can not be trusted as you know.
They might've set up a trap.
Do not worry Gunduz Bey.
Let them set their traps.
My Allah is greater than them.
I am thinking about the future.
You will see, after this marriage
we will heal all our wounds.
You will smile like before too.
Aunt?
Aunt, what happened?
Are you alright? Aunt?
Aunt? Help us!
-My girl, what is happening here?
-Ayca?
-What happened?
-Mother, Gonca..
..bring her up and make her vomit, I'll be back.
-Come on.
Come on aunt.
Alps! Send word to healers, let them come here!
Doctors?
-What's going on, my Shahzade? -Wait here.
-Did she puke, mother?
-Yes, she did. Look.
What is it, son? Poison?
Not good, mother. She's poisoned.
Poisoned?
-What poison?
-I don't know, Gonca.
We need to find first the poison and then the cure.
Or we will lose Ayca Hatun.
What happened here, Elcim Hatun?
It happened after she drank water.
Water?
Gonca Hatun, make her drink this.
It will relieve her pains for a while.
-Open her mouth, Bala Hatun.
-Bring it.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
O Healer!
-O Healer!
-Drink it.
Who would poison you and why?
They were going to poison
me but my aunt got poisoned.
Help us, my Allah.
-What's going on?
-You...
You did this. You wanted to kill. My aunt is dying!
-What do you think you are saying?
-Still asking?
You wanted to poison me but poisoned my aunt!
You're blinded by your
anger. I didn't poison anyone.
-There are no other enemies but you here!
-Pull yourself together.
-Aunt!
-My lady!
My lady!
Holofira... Holofira! Holofira.
Holofira. Holofira. Holofira!
Open your eyes, Holofira.
Inform doctors and Alaaddin!
Elcim Hatun, what have you done?
I knew you would come with empty hands, Osman Bey.
You know me well.
I brought you only blood and bones.
What? Will you protect yourself with these?
I invited you here so you could deliver the signs.
-To talk.
-Are you hiding behind the prisoners?
Not only by using the prisoners,
...but also by killing all the
warriors and beys in the tribe.
See my strength and don't
stand in my way, Osman Bey.
You will give me the signs.
If I know you a little, you
must have hidden them already.
I don't want to kill you. Because
only you must know where they are.
You will never be able to find the signs.
-Ever.
-Well... If you say so...
Then I will kill all the prisoners.
"Osman Bey sacrificed women and children....
...for a few ancient items", people will say.
-And you'll walk with shame.
-I will take the prisoners from you.
You'll talk about the Crusader
army to come to my lands.
You arranged an agreement
between Olcaytu and Crusaders.
Now tell me.
Which countries in the east
are going to join the campaign?
Give me what is mine Osman. Right now!
You have nothing to take from these lands.
I will destroy both you and those Crusader looters!
The only thing you will take
will be my sword of justice.
Visit turkision.com for more!